Finding Aid for First Unitarian-Universalist Church Records
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
First Unitarian-Universalist Church of Detroit Records 1845-2012
First Unitarian-Universalist Church of Detroit.
2014057 Ba 2
The First Unitarian-Universalist Church of Detroit Records comprise over 150 years of records documenting the activities of the church's ministers, administrative bodies, committees and interest groups, and members. The first such denomination in the Detroit area, First U-U traces its history to the mid-nineteenth century and represents the convergence of two like-minded denominations founded on principles of humanism, social consciousness, and civic responsibility. The collection's five series contain materials pertaining to the church's history and development, administration, religious services, educational programs, and community engagement.
22 linear feet
1 oversize boxes
1 oversize folders
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
The records were donated by The First Unitarian-Universalist Church of Detroit (Donor No. 10908 ) in 2013.
Periodic additions to the records expected.
The collection is open to research.
The First Unitarian-Universalist Church of Detroit was formed with the merger of two local denominations with a common mission of social progressivism and skepticism towards religious dogma. The church's early history may be traced to the First Congregational Unitarian Society of Detroit, which was founded in 1850 and known then as the Railroad Church due to its membership being comprised largely of railroad workers. Local Universalist and Unitarian congregations were officially incorporated as churches in 1880 and 1890, respectively. The present church building was erected in 1916 as the First Universalist Church (Church of Our Father). Following a successful temporary union in 1932, a binding legal agreement joined the Unitarian and Universalist congregations permanently, thus forming the Unitarian-Universalist Church of Our Father in 1934. In 1960, the church's name was officially changed to the First Unitarian-Universalist Church of Detroit, one year before the two denominations consolidated on the national level to form the Unitarian Universalist Association (UUA).
The church's long history of social justice work began in the 1850s when Unitarian Reverend Thomas J. Mumford expressed public opposition to capital punishment and the Fugitive Slave Act. Church activities and civic engagement efforts have long been guided by its foundational principles, which include freedom of thought, the importance of individual spiritual and intellectual development, service to the community, and inclusivity. First U-U maintains group memberships in the ACLU, NAACP, and Planned Parenthood. Its current mission is to serve as an urban center for spiritual renewal and social justice in Detroit, in addition to continuing its worship and religious education initiatives.
The First Unitarian-Universalist Church of Detroit Records comprise the collected documentation of the activities of the church's administrative bodies, committees, and congregation members. The collection contains materials pertaining to the church's history and development, governance, and religious, educational, and community service activities. The collection is divided into five series: Ministry and Membership, Church Administration, Church Committees and Organizations, Church Activities, and Newsletters and Orders of Service.
Subjects:
First Congregational Unitarian Society (Detroit, Mich.); First Unitarian-Universalist Church of Detroit.; First Unitarian Universalist Society (Detroit, Mich.); Detroit (Mich.)--Church history.; Unitarian Universalist churches--Education.; Unitarian Universalist churches--History.; Unitarian Universalist churches--Michigan--Detroit.; Unitarianism--History.; Universalism--History.
Genre Terms:
Photographs.; Scrapbooks.
- Ministry and Membership
  The Ministry and Membership series (2.5 linear feet) is divided into two subseries (Ministers and Membership). The former subseries is composed of minister's sermons, correspondence, photographs, and documents pertaining to ministerial searches. The records of ministers Rudolf C. (Rudi) Gelsey, Larry G. Hutchinson, Tracy Pullman, and Augustus P. Reccord are particularly well-represented. The latter subseries contains membership directories, records of birth, death, and marriage, photographs, and press clippings pertaining to particular church members.
  - Ministers
    - Stan Aronson, photographs 1985 (Box 1)
    - Emmy-Lou Belcher, ordination photographs 1989 (Box 1)
    - Terasa G. Cooley, sermons 1991-1992 (Box 1)
    - T.B. Forbush, sermons 1885 (Box 1)
    - Rudolf C. (Rudi) Gelsey
      - Sermons 1970s-1980s (Box 1)
      - Installation correspondence 1973 (Box 1)
      - Evaluations 1975, 1980, 1982 (Box 1)
    - Richard Hasty, sermons 1988-1989 (Box 1)
    - Larry G. Hutchinson
      - Biographical materials 1980s-2003 (Box 1)
      - Ministerial search survey undated (Box 1)
      - Installation photographs 1995, 2 folders (Box 1)
      - Certificates and related correspondence 1989-1995 (Box 1)
    - T.J. Mumford, ordination remarks 1851 (Box 1)
    - Anthony R. Perrino
      - Sermons 1960s-1970s (Box 1)
      - Newspaper articles 1969, 1972 (Box 1)
    - Tracy Pullman
      - Sermons
        - Vol. I 1925-1930, 4 folders (Box 1)
        - Vol. II 1930-1932, 4 folders (Box 1)
        - 1956, 1963 undated (Box 1)
      - Correspondence
        - 1941, 3 folders (Box 1)
        - 1942, 3 folders (Box 1)
        - 1943, 3 folders (Box 1)
        - 1945-1957, undated (Box 1)
      - Farewell tribute 1968 (Box 1)
    - Augustus P. Reccord
      - Annual minister's reports 1935-1939 (Box 1)
      - Sermons undated (Box 1)
      - Correspondence 1925 (Box 1)
      - Scrapbook of newspaper articles 1886-1915, 1932 (Box 1)
    - Reed Stuart, sermons 1900, 1901 (Box 2)
    - Assorted ministers, sermons 1881 undated (Box 2)
    - Assorted ministers (Mumford, Reccord, Stuart, Pullman), photographs 1852, 1900 undated (Box 2)
    - Assorted ministers, photographs, 20th century (Box 2)
    - Installation services, programs 1869, 1906, 1919, 1940, 1968-1996 (Box 2)
    - Ministerial search committee
      - Minutes and correspondence 1923 (Box 2)
      - Information packets for prospective ministers
        - 1985 (Box 2)
        - 1989 (Box 2)
        - 1994 (Box 2)
  - Membership
    - Membership rosters (bound) 1934-1949, 1948-1960, 1961-1977 (Box 2)
    - Directories
      - 1888, 1891, 1899, 1900, 1907 (Box 2)
      - 1913, 1923, 1935, 1940, 1951, 1952 (Box 2)
      - 1955-1959 (Box 2)
      - 1961-1963 (Box 2)
      - 1964-1967, 1969-1970 (Box 2)
      - 1972-1977 (Box 2)
      - 1981, 1983, 1984, 1987 (Box 2)
      - 1990, 1994-1997, 1999, 2001, 2010 undated (Box 2)
    - Membership lists undated (Box 3)
    - Membership certificates 1989-1991 (Box 3)
    - Membership postcards 1954 (Box 3)
    - Miscellaneous membership records 1965, 1970, 1982, 1988 undated (Box 3)
    - Record of births 1926-1929 (Box 3)
    - Marriage records 1974, 1975, 1991, 1992 (Box 3)
    - Pastor's wedding and funeral record book 1970-1974 (Box 3)
    - Memorial services
      - 1915-1918 (Box 3)
      - 1970s-1990s, 2 folders (Box 3)
    - Obituaries 1970s-1990s, 2010 (Box 3)
    - Memorial funds 1976, 1986, 1989 (Box 3)
    - Photographs of members
      - Anne Pawlik (farewell party), circa 1990 (Box 3)
      - Anne Pawlik (winning City Council award) undated (Box 3)
      - Don and Ardith (farewell party) 1990s (Box 3)
      - Judge Wade McCree memorial service undated (Box 3)
      - Assorted members (identified) 1960s-1990s, 2 folders (Box 3)
      - Assorted members (unidentified) 1906, 1960s-2000s (Box 3)
    - Press clippings pertaining to particular members 1960s-1990s (Box 3)
- Church Administration
  The Church Administration series (6.3 linear feet) is divided into seven subseries: Administrative Records, Board of Directors, Church Council, Church Trust, Congregational Meetings, Church History, and The Unitarian-Universalist Church at the National Level.
  - Administrative Records
    The first subseries contains records pertaining to church administration at the highest level, which include church constitutions and bylaws, mortgages and other property records, financial records, and administrative correspondence.
    - Constitution and bylaws
      - 1919 (Box 3)
      - 1950s-1960s (Box 3)
      - 1970s-1980s (Box 3)
      - 1990s, 2006 (Box 3)
    - Articles of association 1921, 1934, 1948 undated (Box 3)
    - Mission and vision statements undated (Box 3)
    - Property records
      - Mortgages and other property records 1852, 1861, 1905, 1921, 1933-1935 (Box 3)
      - Records of indenture 1933-1934 (Box 3)
      - Miscellaneous property records 1934-1935, 1963-1964 (Box 3)
    - Financial records
      - Financial policies and procedures 1991 (Box 3)
      - Treasurer's reports and other financial documents
        - 1870-1872 (Box 3)
        - 1893-1903, undated (Box 3)
      - Ledger book 1922-1941 (Box 3)
      - Development campaigns 1959, 1963, 1966 (Box 3)
      - Canvass brochures 1978, 1979, 1992 (Box 3)
      - Miscellaneous financial records 1859, 1870s, 1900, 1903, 1917, 1933-1935 (Box 3)
    - Staff lists and organizational charts 1960s, 1980s undated (Box 3)
    - Church "dictionary," undated (Box 3)
    - Assorted administrative correspondence 1873, 1891, 1899-1912, 1921, 1934, 1956, 1966 (Box 3)
  - Board of Directors
    The second subseries contains the records of the church's governing body, which has been known alternately as the Board of Directors, Board of Trustees, and the Governing Board. This subseries predominantly consists of meeting minutes, reports to the Board, policy documents, and correspondence.
    - Board policies
      - 1993 (Box 4)
      - 2010 (Box 4)
      - Policy manual 2005-2006 (Box 4)
    - Miscellaneous reports 1919, 1934-1935 (Box 4)
    - Minutes
      - 1870s, 1895, 1904, 1910 (Box 4)
      - 1880-1900 (bound) (Box 4)
      - 1900-1910 (bound) (Box 4)
      - 1901-1923 (bound) (Box 4)
      - 1913-1920 (bound) (Box 4)
      - 1931-1934 (bound) (Box 4)
      - 1932-1937 (Box 4)
      - 1938-1944 (Box 4)
      - 1946-1949 (Box 4)
      - 1950 (Box 4)
      - 1951 (Box 4)
      - 1952 (Box 4)
      - 1953-1954 (Box 4)
      - 1955-1956 (Box 4)
      - 1957-1958 (Box 4)
      - 1959 (Box 4)
      - 1960 (Box 4)
      - 1961 (Box 4)
      - 1962 (Box 4)
      - 1963 (Box 4)
      - 1964 (Box 4)
      - 1965 (Box 4)
      - 1966 (Box 5)
      - 1967 (Box 5)
      - 1968-1969 (Box 5)
      - 1970-1972 (Box 5)
      - 1975-1976 (Box 5)
      - 1977-1978 (Box 5)
      - 1979 (Box 5)
      - 1980 (Box 5)
      - 1981 (Box 5)
      - 1982 (Box 5)
      - 1983 (Box 5)
      - 1984 (Box 5)
      - 1985 (Box 5)
      - 1986 (Box 5)
      - 1987 (Box 5)
      - 1988, 3 folders (Box 5)
      - 1989, 3 folders (Box 5)
      - 1990, 3 folders (Box 5)
      - 1991, 2 folders (Box 6)
      - 1992, 2 folders (Box 6)
      - 1993 (Box 6)
      - 1994 (Box 6)
      - 1995, 2 folders (Box 6)
      - 1996 (Box 6)
      - 1997 (Box 6)
      - 1998 (Box 6)
      - 1999-2003 (Box 6)
      - 2004 (Box 6)
      - 2005 (Box 6)
      - 2006-2008 (Box 6)
      - 2009 (Box 6)
      - 2010, 2 folders (Box 6)
      - 2011-2012 (Box 6)
    - Miscellaneous correspondence
      - 1877, 1902-1905, 1920, 1930s, 1953 (Box 6)
      - 1914-1916 (Box 6)
      - 1917 (Box 6)
    - Assorted board records 1980s-2000s (Box 6)
    - Board members, photographs 1993 undated (Box 6)
    - Leadership retreat, photographs 1990s (Box 6)
  - Church Council
    The third subseries contains meeting minutes and annual reports of the Church Council.
    - Annual reports 1960s-1970s, 1989, 1997-2000s (Box 6)
    - Annual meetings, minutes and reports 1920s, 1940s, 1950s, 1966 (Box 7)
    - Minutes
      - 1923-1931 (Box 7)
      - 1934-1945 (bound) (Box 7)
      - 1945-1951 (bound) (Box 7)
      - 1951-1952 (Box 7)
      - 1953-1954 (Box 7)
      - 1955-1957 (Box 7)
      - 1958 (Box 7)
      - 1959 (Box 7)
      - 1960 (Box 7)
      - 1961 (Box 7)
      - 1962 (Box 7)
      - 1963 (Box 7)
      - 1964 (Box 7)
      - 1965 (Box 7)
      - 1966 (Box 7)
      - 1967 (Box 7)
      - 1968 (Box 7)
      - 1969 (Box 7)
      - 1975-1977 (Box 7)
      - 1978-1979 (Box 7)
    - Church Council retreat, photographs 1972 (Box 7)
  - Church Trust
    The fourth subseries consists of Church Trust meeting minutes, declarations of trust, assorted financial records, and correspondence.
    - Declarations of trust 1964, 1983 undated (Box 7)
    - Minutes
      - 1905-1909 (Box 7)
      - 1935-1939 (Box 7)
      - 1940-1944 (Box 7)
      - 1945-1965 (bound) (Box 7)
    - Minutes and financial records 1997-1999 (Box 8)
    - Correspondence 1969 (Box 8)
    - Assorted documents
      - 1910, 1934-1935, 1943, 1950-1963 (Box 8)
      - 1964-1969 (Box 8)
      - 1970-1974 (Box 8)
  - Congregational Meetings
    The fifth subseries contains minutes, reports, and other documentation of the proceedings of annual congregational meetings.
    - Minutes
      - 1951-1962 (Box 8)
      - 1963-1969 (Box 8)
      - 1970-1974 (Box 8)
      - 1975-1981 (Box 8)
      - 1982-1988, 1990s (Box 8)
      - 2000-2011 (Box 8)
    - Photographs 1969, 2000 (Box 8)
    - Parish meetings, minutes and reports 1929-1935 (Box 8)
  - Church History
    The sixth subseries contains some of the earliest extant documentation of the church, including the founding documents and records of the First Congregational Unitarian Society of Detroit, and other materials related to the church's formation. This subseries also contains historical overviews and records pertaining to the history of church buildings and property, including the McAdow House and Ernest M. Skinner Organ.
    - First Congregational Unitarian Society of Detroit
      - Founding documents 1850 (Box 8)
      - Bylaws 1868, 1879, 1921 (Box 8)
      - Assorted records 1858-1890s, 1900-1902, 1925 (Box 8)
    - Merger of the First Congregational Unitarian Society of Detroit and the First Universalist Church of Detroit
      - Articles of association/federation 1930s (Box 8)
      - Correspondence 1932-1934 (Box 8)
      - Assorted documents 1933-1935, 1940, 1941 (Box 8)
    - First Unitarian-Universalist Church histories
      - Historical overviews undated (Box 8)
      - Anecdotal histories 1916, 1920 undated (Box 8)
      - Archival materials
        - Document inventory 1849-1993, undated (Box 8)
        - Archives of the First Unitarian-Universalist Church, correspondence 1990 (Box 8)
        - Resources for preserving congregational archives undated (Box 8)
    - Church buildings
      - Building policies undated (Box 8)
      - State Registry of Historic Sites, correspondence 1976-1977 (Box 8)
      - Historic district, proposals and correspondence 1980, 1981 (Box 8)
      - New church buildings, planning 1914-1915 (Box 8)
      - Architectural drawings
        - 1915, 1947, 1983 (Box 8)
        - Undated (Box 8)
      - Photographs
        - 1870s-1900 (Box 8)
        - Undated (Box 8)
      - Stained glass windows, records and correspondence 1950s, 1991 (Box 8)
      - Miscellaneous architectural records 1934, 1970s-1980s, 2000s undated (Box 8)
      - McAdow House
        - Original owner's papers 1892, 1980s undated (Box 8)
        - Assorted documents 1969, 1982 undated (Box 8)
        - Historic houses of worship tours 1981, 1988, 2011 (Box 8)
      - Skinner Organ (Box 9)
        - Histories 1901, 1986, 1994, 2009 (Box 9)
        - Repair and restoration records 1974-1984 (Box 9)
      - Church music histories 1988 undated (Box 9)
  - The Unitarian-Universalist Church at the National Level
    The seventh and last subseries concerns the Unitarian-Universalist Church as a national organization, and contains records of the national Unitarian-Universalist merger, conference photographs, and assorted records from other Unitarian-Universalist churches, mainly in Michigan.
    - Unitarian-Universalist Merger
      - Merger and alternatives (manual) 1958 (Box 9)
      - Consolidation plan 1959 (Box 9)
      - Report of the coordinating committee on consolidation 1961 (Box 9)
      - Assorted documents 1960-1961 (Box 9)
    - Conferences
      - Center City Church Conference (Philadelphia)
        - Program 1972 (Box 9)
        - Preparatory documents 1972 (Box 9)
        - Photographs 1972 (Box 9)
      - Columbus General Assembly, photographs 1984 (Box 9)
      - Denver General Assembly, photographs 1967 (Box 9)
      - Indianapolis General Assembly, photographs 1996 (Box 9)
      - Lake Geneva Unitarian Summer Assembly, photographs 1941, 1942 (Box 9)
      - The Universalist Convention (Tufts College), photographs 1941 (Box 9)
      - Unspecified assemblies, photographs 1950s (Box 9)
    - Committees and associations, assorted documents 1950s-1960s (Box 9)
    - Other Unitarian-Universalist Churches
      - Birmingham Unitarian Church (Bloomfield Hills, MI), records 1957-1959 (Box 9)
      - Unitarian-Universalist Church of East Liberty (Clark Lake, MI)
        - Sermons and services 1986 (Box 9)
        - Orders of service 1966, 1980s (Box 9)
        - Newsletters and events programs 1985-1986 (Box 9)
        - Photographs 1980s (Box 9)
      - First Unitarian-Universalist Church of Lyons, OH, orders of service 1980s (Box 9)
      - Community Church of New York, newsletters 1981-1987, 2 folders (Box 9)
      - Assorted Unitarian-Universalist churches, sermons and essays 1980s-1990s (Box 9)
      - Assorted Unitarian-Universalist churches, pamphlets and orders of service 1928, 1950s-1980s (Box 9)
- Church Committees and Organizations
  The Church Committees and Organizations series (4.2 linear feet) is composed of materials related to the activities of the church's numerous committees, clubs, and interest groups. It is divided into four subseries: Committees, Church Clubs, Women's Alliance (National Alliance of Unitarian and Other Liberal Christian Women), and Other Women's Groups.
  - Committees
    The first subseries consists of minutes, reports, and events programming for twelve committees organized around church management, ministry, and community service. Records of the Worship Committee, which is responsible for planning worship services, church activities, and attending to the needs of the congregation, comprise the bulk of this subseries.
    - Administration and Personnel Committee
      - Minutes and reports 1996-2004 (Box 9)
      - Personnel policy manual 2009 (Box 9)
      - Correspondence 1987-1988 (Box 9)
    - Black Concerns Working Group
      - Events and activities 1988, 1990s (Box 9)
      - Newspaper clippings 1989 undated (Box 9)
      - "An interpathic interpretation of African-American male alienation from the church," by Darryl W. Robinson 2000 (Box 9)
      - Birmingham Unitarian Church/First U-U Church of Detroit Coalition, minutes and activities 1999, 2000 (Box 9)
    - Buildings and Grounds Committee, minutes 1995-1999, 2004 (Box 9)
    - Development Committee, minutes and events 1997-2000, 2003, 2004 (Box 9)
    - Membership and Growth Committee, minutes (Box 10)
      - 1996-1998 (Box 10)
      - 2007, 2010 (Box 10)
    - Ministerial Advisory Committee 1973-1988 (Box 10)
    - Ministry, Committee on, reports 1987-1988 (Box 10)
    - Operating Committee, minutes and reports 1933-1934 (Box 10)
    - Service Committee
      - Minutes 1912-1914 (Box 10)
      - Correspondence and reports 1967-1977 (Box 10)
      - Taskforce for mental health 1963-1964 (Box 10)
      - Wayne County General Hospital program 1964 (Box 10)
    - Social Responsibility Committee 1950s-1960s (Box 10)
    - Ways and Means Committee 1947-1951 (Box 10)
    - Worship Committee
      - Annual reports 1979-1980 (Box 10)
      - Mass attendance records 1980s-1997 (Box 10)
      - Minutes and related records
        - 1979-1988 (Box 10)
        - 1987-1989 (Box 10)
        - 1993-1994 (Box 10)
        - 1995 (Box 10)
        - 1996 (Box 10)
        - 1997-2000 (Box 10)
        - 2001 (Box 10)
        - 2002 (Box 10)
        - 2003 (Box 10)
        - 2004, 2005, 2011 (Box 10)
      - Activities
        - Children's music 1989 undated (Box 10)
        - Congregational surveys 1960s, 2005 (Box 10)
        - Performing artists 1980-1983 (Box 10)
        - Sermons 1980-1984, undated (Box 10)
        - Service ideas 1978, 1980s undated (Box 10)
        - Service schedules 1995 (Box 10)
        - Speakers 1983-1986 (Box 10)
        - Survey report 2002 (Box 10)
        - Ushering 1986, 1994-1996, undated (Box 10)
        - Worship schedule topics 2001-2003 (Box 10)
      - Reference materials
        - Bible information undated (Box 10)
        - Leadership retreat 1994, 1995 (Box 10)
        - Leading congregations in worship: a guide 1983 (Box 10)
        - Readings 1980s (Box 10)
        - Assorted reference materials for worship leaders undated (Box 10)
    - Unspecified Committees
      - Record of committee activities 1985-1994 (Box 10)
      - Annual reports 1897-1919 (Box 10)
      - Miscellaneous committee reports 1903, 1914, 1921, 1928, 1935-1939 (Box 10)
      - Membership lists 1992, 1993 undated (Box 10)
      - Miscellaneous committee correspondence 1890-1899, 1918, 1919, 1934 (Box 10)
      - Assorted committee records 1920s, 1940s, 1990s undated (Box 10)
      - Photographs 1956, 1960, 1984, 1989 undated (Box 10)
  - Church Clubs
    The second subseries consists of minutes, reports, correspondence, membership rosters, and events programming for 17 clubs organized around various constituencies (youth and students, women) and around artistic, cultural, and community service pursuits.
    - Arista Club (Box 11)
      - Reports 1939 (Box 11)
      - Scrapbook (events, newspaper clippings, members) 1926-1930 (Box 11)
    - Busy Bee Serving Society, membership directory undated (Box 11)
    - Channing Club and College Club assorted records 1940s-1950s (Box 11)
    - Charity Club, annual reports 1895-1897 (Box 11)
    - Community Ministry, minutes and reports 2004 (Box 11)
    - Couple's Club, membership lists 1960s (Box 11)
    - Doublets Club, minutes and reports 1936-1944 (Box 11)
    - Double-U Club, minutes and records 1930s-1960s (Box 11)
    - The Drama Group, assorted records 1959-1962 (Box 11)
    - Fireside Group, reports 1925-1926, 1930s, 1940, 1944 (Box 11)
    - Fortnightly Club, reports and events 1899-1901 (Box 11)
    - Laymen's League
      - Reports and correspondence
        - 1910, 1919, 1930s-1940s, 1952 (Box 11)
        - 1966-1968 (Box 11)
      - Lay leader notebook undated (Box 11)
      - Reference resources for lay leaders 1974, 1987 (Box 11)
    - The Mission Circle, minutes
      - 1917-1924 (Box 11)
      - 1925-1929 (Box 11)
      - 1932-1940 (Box 11)
    - Multiple Arts Club, minutes and events 1957-1959 (Box 11)
    - Parent Teacher Association assorted records 1934-1937, 1940 (Box 11)
    - Unity Club, assorted records 1881, 1895-1910 (Box 11)
    - Young People's Religious Union
      - Reports and programs 1906, 1918, 1919 (Box 11)
      - Detroit '97 convention 1897 (Box 11)
    - Miscellaneous church groups, annual reports 1903-1904, 1925, 1936-1937 (Box 11)
  - Women's Alliance (National Alliance of Unitarian and Other Liberal Christian Women)
    The third subseries contains administrative records, annual programs, member directories, minutes, reports, and subcommittee records for one of the church's most prominent women's groups.
    - Bylaws 1965, 1981 (Box 11)
    - Manuals
      - 1926-1927 (Box 11)
      - 1936-1937 (Box 11)
    - Organizational history 1986 (Box 11)
    - Annual programs
      - 1911-1942 (Box 11)
      - 1964-1979 (Box 11)
      - 1981-1989, 2004-2008 (Box 11)
    - Reports